

💌 jamie@jamielocatis.com 🤡 www.jamielocatis.com 📞 (402) 681-8061 👂 2315 Harney Street #201, Omaha, NE 68102

y jamielocatis **in** linkedin.com/in/jlocatis **⊙** jlocatis

summary

I am a creative, passionate developer who is enthusiastic about continuously learning new skills and technologies. I bring together seven years of senior management, business operations, and team building expertise with well-rounded software development skills to benefit the creation of engaging, human-centric applications.



+ projects

Omaha Barcamp Scheduler (ReactJS, Rails, PostgreSQL)

Scheduling application for the annual Omaha Barcamp meetup. Guests schedule talks on-site during the day of the event. Uses ReactJS for live updating of the site across all devices accessing it. Guests can schedule their impromptu talks the day of and view a current schedule. Uses Rails as a backend API for accessing the database.

Omaha Theatre Arts Guild Awards (Ruby, Rails, PostgreSQL)

An application that allows Omaha Theatre Arts Guild members to both nominate and vote in their annual TAG Awards. Administrators have special access to update lists of available artists, plays, and roles for nomination throughout the year. The many steps through the actual awards process are completely handled by the application. This includes allowing each user to nominate up to 140 total potential nominations (5 each from 28 categories), letting the TAG board select the final ballot, and serving that ballot to members. All calculations based on the Omaha Theatre Arts Guild's specific weighting system are handled by the application.

Student Work Tracking (Ruby, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Sinatra)

Omaha Code School was seeking a process to have students periodically post updates of their work status with minimal interruption. As an equal member of a three person team, we developed a site where students can post work updates throughout the day along with alerting the instructor if they are in need of assistance. Instructors may search posts by student/date. Additional features included a live feed for students of daily updates and GitHub API integration.

employment

Greenville, SC QuikTrip

New Store Opening Manager

2012 to 2016

- As a member of the initial market entry team, helped to grow QuikTrip's presence to over 30 locations in under 5 years.
- Played a key role in the market's growth through the training and development of hundreds of employees, promoting over 25 into store management roles and beyond.
- Integral team member in the development of community and vendor relations.
- Engaged and inspired a team of 50+ employees.

Omaha, NE

Store Manager

2009 to 2012

- In charge of overseeing day to day business operations, including the Omaha metro market's highest volume store.
- · Conducted team meetings and employee evaluations, fostering a team spirited environment.
- Ensured customer and team satisfaction while creating a fast-paced, energetic work environment that delivered a consistent QuikTrip brand experience.
- Additional business management duties included: maintaining and explaining P&L & budgeting, inventory control, vendor relations, and maintaining product margins.

education

Omaha Code School Certificate Web Development 2017

University of Nebraska at Omaha Completed courses in Computer Science.

Creighton University

Completed courses in Integrated Leadership Studies.

Omaha North High School 2005

skills

Rubv

Rails

JavaScript

ReactJS

HTML5 CSS3

PostgreSQL

AJAX

Git/GitHub

JSON

Photoshop

Illustrator

Sinatra RSpec

Jest/Enzyme

ASP.NET MVC

Unix Shell

Cisco CCNA

volunteering

United Way of Greenville County Greenville, SC

2013 to 2016

Assisted in the organization of United Way of Greenville County's annual Hands on Greenville volunteer weekend. For two years (2015-2016) acted as a liaison between both QuikTrip and Target's local involvement and sponsorship with the event. Coordinated the weekend's volunteer events with Greenville County Animal Care, with both QuikTrip and Target acting as primary sponsors at that location.

Omaha. NE